Akshay Kumar

Contact No. - 9719357960

Email I'd - Panwarakshay08@gmail.com

Process Associate

My name is Akshay Kumar and I have done BSc. Computer Science from Meerut College and I have 2+ years of experience. I have 1 year of exp. In Capgemini India Pvt Ltd as Process Associate and 1.4 years as Document Specialist in Aptara International Pvt Ltd.



F - Block Sector 40, Noida, Uttar Pradesh, India

Work Experience

Process Associate · Capgemini India Private Limited

I have to enroll the members in the health Care plan as per their request and analyze, every information which is given and stored in the CMS portal, and maintain the client information without modification on the details and maintaining the record.

September 2022 - December 2022

Document Specialist · Aptara International Pvt Ltd

I have to modify the US SEC filling documents modifications using MS office 365 as per their request and these modification is done by using Word, Excel & PowerPoint.

April 2021 - August 2022

Process Associate · Capgemini India Pvt Ltd

I have to enroll the members in the health plan as per their request and analyze every information which is given and stored in the CMS portal, and maintain the client information without modifications to the details and maintaining the record.

August 2020 - March 2021

Education



2015 - 2018

Modern Public School

Computer Science Intermediate Science stream with Mathematics



2012 - 2013

Modern Public School

High School

2014 - 2015

Modern Public School

Intermediate

Skills

- MS office 365
- · Strong Interpersonal Skills
- Innovative
- Leadership

Languages

- English Intermediate
- Hindi Native or Bilingual

Powered by **CakeResume**